GERARD MORENO

Desktop Support Technician

Pittsburg, CA

gerard.moreno@outlook.com

9252820735

Highly competent and dedicated IT technician with over four years of IT experience. Utilizes outstanding professional communication and support to clients and users. Maintains high standards for user satisfaction and ensures all projects are completed in a timely manner.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer



WORK EXPERIENCE

Google Field Technician

Premium Retail Services - San Francisco, CA January 2019 to Present

Performed service order requests via a ticketing system.

Display setup and installation of Google demo devices.

Troubleshooting and repairs at client locations as needed.

Documented all service orders and repairs.

Desktop Support Technician

Muirtech - Martinez, CA January 2017 to April 2019

Performed daily on-site and remote computer network maintenance

services, troubleshooting, and repairs.

Prioritized and performed technical support requests via RMM Software.

Documented computer and server support tickets.

Installed and configured new servers and computers as needed.

Performed new software installations and updates. Windows 7, 8, 10 professional. Windows Server 2008 R2, 2010, 2012 and 2016. MS Exchange 2007, 2010, 2013 and 2016. Mac OS 10.12, 10.13, 10.14. iPhone and Android. SQL server 2016, Active Directory, MS Azure.

Fleet Support Technician

Ricoh - San Francisco, CA March 2015 to January 2017

Daily support of workstation and printers. Responds to customer support requests and ensures that they are resolved quickly, accurately, and professionally. Escalates problems to higher level technician when necessary. Provided users with remote access and complete troubleshooting. Managed printer hot swap inventory and consumables.



EDUCATION

BA in Business in Information Systems Management

Diablo Valley College - Pleasant Hill, CA April 2015 to January 2021



SKILLS

- Desktop Support
- Help Desk
- Network Support
- Computer Repair
- Comptia



----- CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

Driver's License

CompTIA A+



ASSESSMENTS

Basic Computer Skills: PC — Highly Proficient

August 2019

Performing basic computer operations, navigating a Windows OS, and troubleshooting common computer problems. Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_to_profile/0ce67795d05056e4b21604b6a8c56d85

Customer Focus & Orientation — Highly Proficient

December 2018

Measures a candidate's ability to respond to customer situations with sensitivity.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share to profile/2d19b83e57553f44b8bf5eaa93776556eed53dc074545cb7

Technical Support — Highly Proficient

September 2019

Performing software, hardware, and network operations.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_assignment/vzac3y1ixr32s-zs

Cognitive Ability — Highly Proficient

November 2019

Measures a candidate's ability to combine pieces of information to form general rules or conclusions.

 $\textbf{Full results:} \ \underline{\text{https://share.indeedassessments.com/share to profile/}}$

804f68c05551db8ca4c603119f772b33eed53dc074545cb7

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.